-Built inside a glass house on a height in the forest near Lake Vänern beach.
Could it be an example of the accommodation of the future?
At least it believes Anders Solvarm, whose natural villa has built the house.
Now we are in a wooden house, you might say.
We try to build with materials that store carbon dioxide.
Wood sucks the carbon dioxide in the air and then it is stored.
Actually, it is a regular residential building that we move in.
But when you go out into this space-
-Between outdoors and residential part, you end up in a garden.
Electricity and heat come from the sun during the summer.
In winter, batteries are recharged using biodiesel.
There is no connection to the mains.
-As they can tolerate a little frost.
There will be a little frost here in the winter.
It's just a single glass.
It rains, snows or never blows.
But it gets cool and cold in winter.
Not as cold as outside, but it can be minus degrees.
Almost SEK 8 million costs it for those who want to put the mittens on the house-
-As is currently out for sale.
The economy is that you do not receive any invoice.
So the house costs nothing, besides having to buy some firewood in winter-
-and some biodiesel to charge your batteries.
Extremely low operating costs.
In a longer perspective, it is often the large cost of the house.
Maintenance and operating costs are very small.
It is an expensive investment that pays off in the longer term.
When the really hot, hot summer days-
-We need to have shade.
Here we stand under a small shadow wall.
The best shade is obtained when the wine has grown up.
The wine is going up here.
In addition to the leaves giving shadow-
-So they transpire.
They are eating water vapor.
Then the temperature is lowered in the air.
Energy goes to evaporate.
Perspire.
It's kind of like when we sweat.
Then the temperature is lowered.
Shade, plants and ventilation, then it will be nice.